Now let me show you what happens if we don't use the await keyword here.
现在我来展示一下如果这里不使用 await 关键字会怎么样
We're not telling our code to stop.
我们不告诉代码这里需要停下来
We're saying hey, deploy this contract and then just keep going.
这样我们说的就是，部署这个合约，然后直接继续运行
So we never actually checked to see if this deploy function finished.
结果就是我们完全没有检查这个 "deploy" 函数是否已经执行完成
So let's see what happens when we run this instead.
让我们看看这样运行后发生了些什么
Instead of that big contract object, we get this promise in its pending state
这次我们获得的是 "Promise " 状态而不是一个巨大的合约对象
because our code actually finished before our contract could finish deploying.
这是因为我们的代码在部署完成前就运行完了
So we see promise pending here instead,
所以这里我们看到的是 "Promise "
this is why the await keyword is so important.
这就是为什么 "await" 关键字如此重要
We're saying hey, wait for this to finish
我们是在告诉它，等待这里执行完成
the await keyword also resolves a promise.
await 关键字处理了这个 promise
So it'll wait for the promise to exit it's pending state.
所以它会等待 promise 退出 pending 状态
And then it'll return whatever the pending promise returns.
并返回 promise 在 pending 后返回的任何东西
So contract factory to deploy returns a promise that returns a contract.
所以 "contractFactory.deploy()" 返回的是一个返回合约的 promise
In fact, if we go to the ethers documentation, we look up deploy. And here
事实上，如果我们前往 ethers 的文档，在这里检索 "deploy"
we can see contract factory methods contract factory dot deploy.
我们就能看到 "contractFactory.deploy()" 方法
If we look at the definition of the function,
如果我们看一下这个函数的定义
it says contract factory dot deploy
它说的是 "contractFactory.deploy"
takes a whole bunch of arguments and some overrides
它接收一大堆参数以及一些覆盖选项("overrides")
this arrow is saying this is what it returns,
这个箭头表示的是它返回的是什么
it returns a promise that resolves to a contract.
它返回的是一个实现合约的 promise
And that's why we need this await keyword
这就是为什么我们需要这个 await 关键字
because contract factory to deploy by itself just returns a promise.
因为 "contractFactory.deploy()" 本身只返回一个 promise
But if we do await contract factory dot deploy,
但如果我们变成 "await contractFactory.deploy()"
we're saying it returns a promise that resolves to a contract.
我们做的就是，它返回了一个实现合约的 promise
And we're waiting for it to finish deploying to resolve to a contract object.
并且我们等待它完成部署以实现一个合约对象
So that's gonna be a major difference here.
这就是它们之间的主要差别
Awesome work. So that's gonna be why this await keyword is so important.
干得不错，这就是为什么 await 关键字如此重要
And again, you can only do that in asynchronous functions.
并且再次提醒，只能在异步函数中使用它
So you need this async keyword at the top of your function names.
所以你需要在你的函数名称上方加上 "async" 关键字
Awesome work. So we've deployed a contract to our ganache. Shane, this is fantastic.
干得好，现在我们已经把合约部署到了 Ganache 链上，真是太棒了
Let's play with this a little bit more. So what else can we do?
让我们更进一步，现在我们能做些什么呢？
Remember how in remix and in Metamask, we could add a whole bunch of stuff.
记得在 Remix 和 Metamask 上，我们可以添加很多东西
We could add a gas limit, we could add some value
我们可以添加 gas 上限("gas limit")，可以添加一些价值("value")
when we were doing our trends. that we could press the transact button.
在我们进行交易的时候可以按下交易("Transact")按钮
We know that when we're working with Metamask, and we want to send some money between our accounts,
并且在使用 Metamask 时，我们可以在我们的账户之间发送资金
we can actually choose our gas price, our priority fee, all this other stuff,
我们可以选择 gas 价格("gas price") 优先费("priority fee")，以及所有这些东西
we can actually do all that in ethers as well.
我们也可以在 ethers 中完成这些操作
So if we wanted to await contract factory to deploy, but with a certain gas price,
所以，如果我们想在 "await contractFactory.deploy" 中指定 gas 价格
we can add these overrides in this deploy function here.
我们可以在 deploy 函数这里添加一些 overrides
Another really neat trick that your Visual Studio code might have
另一个在 Visual Studio Code 中可能非常有用的技巧是
is if you click Command or Control,
如果你按住 Command 或者 Ctrl 键
depending on your setup,
具体和你配置相关
you can actually click into a function and see where it's defined
你可以点击进入一个函数并查看它在哪里被定义
and see everything about this function.
并且你可以查看关于这个函数的一切
So if I command clicked,
如果我按住 Command 并点击进入
I could see that I'm now in
可以看到我现在位于
Node modules ethers project contract source of Ts, all this stuff.
"node_modules > @ethersproject > contract > src.ts" 等等所有这些
And I can see exactly the function definition of this deploy function on the contract factory object,
而且我可以看到在 "contractFactory" 对象上的这个 "deploy" 函数的详细定义
which shows us the same code as what we saw in the documentation.
它向我们展示了与我们在文档中看到的相同的代码
We see we have a deploy function, it takes some arguments,
我们看到这是一个 "deploy" 函数，它接收一些参数
and then it returns this little semicolon means it returns a promise that resolves to a contract,
然后返回，这个小冒号表示返回一个实现合约的 promise
which is really nice.
真是不错
These are in here are actually a list of overrides that we can specify with some brackets.
这里的 args 是可以用一组花括号指定的一系列 overrides。
So what we can do
所以我们该怎么做？
is we can put some brackets in our deploy function here and specify certain things
我们可以在 deploy 函数这里放一组花括号并指定一些内容
like for example, we can specify the gas price to being some number.
比如说，我们可以指定 "gasPrice" 为一些数字
And now if we were to run this,
现在如果我们运行它
we would deploy this contract with a gas price of this,
就会以这个 gas 价格部署这个合约
we could add a gas limit, we can add a whole bunch of different overrides
我们还可以添加 "gasLimit"，以及一大堆不同的 overrides
in our deploy function here.
在我们的 deploy 函数这里